fashiontrendsetter.com 2018-12-18

# PRIVACY POLICY ‹ Fashion Trendsetter

## Who we are

Our website address is: <http://www.fashiontrendsetter.com/>

Fashion Trendsetter respects the privacy of our readers. Since we request personal information for some of our online features, this policy summarizes the types of information we will collect and how it will be used.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

While you are free to visit our website, read articles, and use selected features without providing any personal information, we may collect information such as your name and e-mail address as you voluntarily sign up for our [ **Newsletter**](http://www.fashiontrendsetter.com/newsletter/).

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on Fashion Trendsetter may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, links, ads etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

Fashion Trendsetter allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, such as [ **Google AdSense**](https://www.google.com/adsense/), to serve advertisements on FashionTrendsetter.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear within contents of FashionTrendsetter.com and they automatically receive your IP Address and other log file information when this happens. Such third-party ad servers may also use other technologies such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. Certain third-party ad servers, such as Google, may also use these cookies to serve ads to you based on your visits on all sites on the Internet.

Fashion Trendsetter does not provide your Personal Information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Fashion Trendsetter to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience that they were trying to reach. We will -never- sell your information to third parties without your permission.

We may provide general information and statistics, such as click-through rates and user trends to advertisers, but we will not share personal information.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Fashion Trendsetter reserves the right to add or remove third-party ad networks or ad servers in its discretion and Fashion Trendsetter may not at all times list such updated ad network or ad server partners in this Privacy Policy.

If you would like more information about these activities and to know your choices about not having this information used by these third parties, click the following link at:  **<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>**.

## How long we retain your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

* * *

**Google AdSense (Google Inc.)**  
Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Application and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.

Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout.

Place of processing: USA – [**Privacy Policy – Opt Out**](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout)

**  
Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**  
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Google Analytics might use Google’s Interest-based advertising, 3rd-party audience data and information from the DoubleClick Cookie to extend analytics with demographics, interests and ads interaction data.

Place of processing: USA – [**Privacy Policy – Opt Out**](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

**  
Quantcast Measure (Quantcast Corporation)**  
Quantcast Measure is an analytics service provided by Quantcast Corporation.

Place of processing: USA – **[Privacy Policy – Opt Out](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/)**

To receive our e-mail [ **Newsletters**](http://www.fashiontrendsetter.com/newsletter/), you must voluntarily opt-in to our mailing list. We do not buy or sell lists. We maintain personal information and do not give that information out to those third parties. You may opt-out of our mailing list at any time by [ **clicking here**](http://fashiontrendsetter.com/mailman/options/newsletter_fashiontrendsetter.com).

Please note that Fashion Trendsetter’s privacy practices as described above do not apply to the privacy policies or practices of our affiliated programs.

Fashion Trendsetter reserves the right to modify this policy at any time. Thank you for your cooperation.

_This privacy policy was put in effect on May  25, 2018._
